tutzone.org 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy - TutZone

Your privacy is critically important to us. At TutZone we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * **We don’t store personal information**  on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services. Like we might store information of User Behavior on our site so that we can tweak the User Interface of our site accordingly.
  * We aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, TutZone collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type,  **language preference, referring site** , and the date and time of each visitor request. TutZone’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how TutZone’s visitors use its website. From time to time, TutZone may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

TutZone also collects potentially  **personally-identifying information**  like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. TutZone does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to TutZone’s websites choose to interact with TutZone in ways that require TutZone to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that TutZone gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. However, TutZone does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always  **refuse to supply**  personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

TutZone may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, TutZone may monitor the User Behavior on TutZone.com, like what visitors View,  **what they click**  on etc. TutZone may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, TutZone does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

TutZone discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organisations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on TutZone’s behalf or to provide services available at TutZone’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organisations may be located outside of your home country; by using TutZone’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. TutZone will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organisations, as described above,  **TutZone discloses potentially personally-identifying**  and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when TutZone believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of TutZone, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an TutZone website and have supplied your email address, TutZone may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with TutZone and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to  **help us support other users**. TutZone takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. TutZone uses cookies to help TutZone identify and track visitors, their usage of TutZone website, and their website access preferences. TutZone visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using TutZone’s websites, with the  **drawback that certain features of TutZone’s**  websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.tutzone.org.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.tutzone.org and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….

### Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.tutzone.org send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the **third-party ad networks** to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalise the advertising content that you see.

www.tutzone.org has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.tutzone.org’s **privacy policy does not apply to** , and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, TutZone may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in TutZone’s sole discretion. TutZone encourages visitors to frequently check this page  **for any changes to its Privacy Policy**. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
